[music]
[bell]
>> And they be
>> [music]
>> Do it.
>> [singing]
>> Mans make her day.
Mans make her day.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Amangani
Say hi.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Amangani
>> Huh?
>> [music]
>> I'm done.
[music]
[singing]
[laughter]
[music]
>> I wonder [music] if this microphone is
working.
I hope it is. Okay, hi guys. We are off
to Ikilani. We
are attending an event. It's related
down because we didn't know what time it
starts. We should have asked the guy.
Kanye gave us the tickets. Thank you my
friend. So we are off to see some cars.
If you know me from my races then that
those are the cars that we are going to
watch.
The race has already started. It started
at 8:00 in the morning. We are very
late. It's about what?
Quarter to 2:00 now.
We are not late intentionally. We didn't
know what time it starts.
To be fair, but it depends at 8:00 p.m.
like the whole event. Yes, the racing
does end at 2:00 so we might get there
and then the racing will be delayed, but
at least we can see the cars.
Yeah, so we are on the way there and I
can't wait to show you guys what we get
up to.
It's like went wrong
and that's going to be a long drive. It
says something on my watch.
It says we'll get there
at 14:12
in 26 minutes.
So let's get going.
I still want some lemonade.
Don't want this.
Lemonade. Ah, it's fine. Let's go.
Can I have a lemon?
Diaspora, if that's what we usually do
then
This is zero sugar by the way.
Mhm.
>> I've been to
I've been to
I've been wise. Push a little bit
harder.
>> 15 minutes. You know, that's not
alcohol.
>> That is.
>> No.
Oh, that is alcohol.
>> [snorts]
>> Mntwana,
please open for me. Thank you.
Are you going to mix now?
>> Sorry, do I just go straight?
>> Yes, straight.
>> Oh, boy.
Oh, boy.
>> There's even jumping castles.
This would have been so nice for Emma.
This would have been so nice for my
baby.
>> [laughter]
>> You got 24 seconds and it's starting
right
>> [singing and music]
[music]
>> You got 24 seconds.
>> [music]
>> Number 80.
>> Happy birthday [singing] to you. Happy
birth
Let me get you some Let me get you some
more money.
>> [music]
>> So we squish.
>> Squishy squishy.
>> [crying]
>> Let me get you some Let me get you some
juice.
Happy birthday.
>> [laughter]
>> This is Lulu's gift. So this is Lulu's
cake. So, beautiful. I highly recommend
this guy who made it. That is a gift
from my friend. Absolutely love it. It's
a building block type of thing. So, he
can build up stuff.
And this is a gift from mom and dad.
This is a car for Lulu, a Maserati.
And yeah, his balloons shame, they're
dying. But yes.
This is Lulu.
Yeah?
Ooh, no one. Yeah. [screaming]
Happy birthday, big boy.
Happy birthday, boy.
The first door on your right at the
back.
>> [music]
[singing]
[laughter]
>> I see you.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I think it's going to be a challenge.
>> [laughter]
[music]
>> I call this I call THIS THE WASHING
MACHINE.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> HEY HEY HEY HEY YES.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
[music]
[singing]
[music and singing]
[screaming]
[music]
>> I'm on my way to
>> [singing]
>> a team building event and I want to vlog
that. Hopefully I can vlog.
>> [music]
>> Do I turn here?
I'm not sure if I turn.
I don't turn here. I turn in the next
one.
Okay.
I see it now.
Drive through.
I don't know where am I.
Jeremy, don't you want to play it?
>> [laughter]
>> Whenever you're ready.
>> Who wants to kiss it?
Okay, that was close.
That was close.
>> Yeah, I can't even see what I'm
throwing.
>> I think it's this one.
>> Oh, is it this one?
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
[music]
>> I had hope. had hope.
Okay, that's not bad. That's good.
>> [music]
>> She's bringing me drinks.
Yeah. [laughter]
The queen of concentration.
Can you please hold it for me? I'm I'm
eating chips.
Okay, it's fine.
Okay.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> I know. Why do we only get three?
And we are so many.
I think I think he might be lighting.
It's stunning. Yeah.
>> [screaming]
[laughter]
>> Oh.
So we have two shots.
Oh.
>> [laughter]
>> She's leading me with one ball.
[laughter]
>> Okay.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Yes,
finally.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm only left with a black ball. This is
my LAST BALL.
>> [laughter]
>> I SHALL ANOTHER ONE.
YOUR LAST SHOT?
Your last shot, my friend.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Guys, say hi to my channel.
>> [laughter]
>> I like his people.
I am a nice person.
>> Yeah.
>> One of your what?
>> Yes.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh.
Bye.
Let's go home.
It was so much fun, Shane.
It wasn't too bad.
I now need to navigate home. Oh, this
guy wants money, son.
I think I have
some money.
Thank you so much.
Goes.
Oh, it's so hot. Yes, yes.
Bye, my friend.
>> [laughter]
>> My friend is driving in front of me.
My friend is driving in front of me,
Sana, and I need to navigate because
I don't know if Bendy up ahead. Oh, not
here.
That's my friend.
Bye.
>> [screaming]
[laughter]
>> Big mama,
big mama.
>> Yeah.